{"problemsArray": [
  {"answer": "-5", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the addition property of equality to remove the constant.\nx - 4 + 4 \u003d -9 + 4\nx \u003d -5\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\nx - 4 \u003d -9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n4x + 6 - 6 \u003d -6 - 6\n4x \u003d -12\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(4x)/4 \u003d -12/4\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n4x + 6 \u003d -6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\nx + 4 - 4 \u003d 8 - 4\nx \u003d 4\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\nx + 4 \u003d 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-5", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the addition property of equality to remove the constant.\n-7x - 7 + 7 \u003d 28 + 7\n-7x \u003d 35\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(-7x)/-7 \u003d 35/-7\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n-7x - 7 \u003d 28", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n-7x + 3 - 3 \u003d -4 - 3\n-7x \u003d -7\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(-7x)/-7 \u003d -7/-7\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n-7x + 3 \u003d -4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n6x + 1 - 1 \u003d 37 - 1\n6x \u003d 36\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(6x)/6 \u003d 36/6\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n6x + 1 \u003d 37", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n7x + 1 - 1 \u003d -27 - 1\n7x \u003d -28\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(7x)/7 \u003d -28/7\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n7x + 1 \u003d -27", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-7", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the addition property of equality to remove the constant.\n7x - 4 + 4 \u003d -53 + 4\n7x \u003d -49\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(7x)/7 \u003d -49/7\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n7x - 4 \u003d -53", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the addition property of equality to remove the constant.\n2x - 6 + 6 \u003d -2 + 6\n2x \u003d 4\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(2x)/2 \u003d 4/2\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n2x - 6 \u003d -2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n-4x + 2 - 2 \u003d -6 - 2\n-4x \u003d -8\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(-4x)/-4 \u003d -8/-4\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n-4x + 2 \u003d -6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n7x + 7 - 7 \u003d 14 - 7\n7x \u003d 7\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(7x)/7 \u003d 7/7\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n7x + 7 \u003d 14", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-5", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\nx + 5 - 5 \u003d 0 - 5\nx \u003d -5\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\nx + 5 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n-2x + 2 - 2 \u003d -10 - 2\n-2x \u003d -12\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(-2x)/-2 \u003d -12/-2\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n-2x + 2 \u003d -10", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n2x + 2 - 2 \u003d 12 - 2\n2x \u003d 10\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(2x)/2 \u003d 10/2\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n2x + 2 \u003d 12", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n5x + 5 - 5 \u003d 15 - 5\n5x \u003d 10\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(5x)/5 \u003d 10/5\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n5x + 5 \u003d 15", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n-6x + 5 - 5 \u003d -19 - 5\n-6x \u003d -24\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(-6x)/-6 \u003d -24/-6\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n-6x + 5 \u003d -19", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n2x + 6 - 6 \u003d 8 - 6\n2x \u003d 2\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(2x)/2 \u003d 2/2\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n2x + 6 \u003d 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n-4x + 1 - 1 \u003d -15 - 1\n-4x \u003d -16\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(-4x)/-4 \u003d -16/-4\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n-4x + 1 \u003d -15", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the addition property of equality to remove the constant.\n-6x - 2 + 2 \u003d -26 + 2\n-6x \u003d -24\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(-6x)/-6 \u003d -24/-6\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n-6x - 2 \u003d -26", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the addition property of equality to remove the constant.\n-6x - 7 + 7 \u003d -37 + 7\n-6x \u003d -30\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(-6x)/-6 \u003d -30/-6\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n-6x - 7 \u003d -37", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the addition property of equality to remove the constant.\n-4x - 1 + 1 \u003d -9 + 1\n-4x \u003d -8\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(-4x)/-4 \u003d -8/-4\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n-4x - 1 \u003d -9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\nx + 5 - 5 \u003d 9 - 5\nx \u003d 4\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\nx + 5 \u003d 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n7x + 5 - 5 \u003d 33 - 5\n7x \u003d 28\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(7x)/7 \u003d 28/7\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n7x + 5 \u003d 33", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the addition property of equality to remove the constant.\n4x - 2 + 2 \u003d 14 + 2\n4x \u003d 16\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(4x)/4 \u003d 16/4\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n4x - 2 \u003d 14", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n2x + 7 - 7 \u003d 17 - 7\n2x \u003d 10\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(2x)/2 \u003d 10/2\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n2x + 7 \u003d 17", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the addition property of equality to remove the constant.\n3x - 6 + 6 \u003d 15 + 6\n3x \u003d 21\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(3x)/3 \u003d 21/3\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n3x - 6 \u003d 15", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n7x + 7 - 7 \u003d 28 - 7\n7x \u003d 21\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(7x)/7 \u003d 21/7\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n7x + 7 \u003d 28", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-5", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n7x + 2 - 2 \u003d -33 - 2\n7x \u003d -35\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(7x)/7 \u003d -35/7\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n7x + 2 \u003d -33", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n3x + 2 - 2 \u003d 20 - 2\n3x \u003d 18\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(3x)/3 \u003d 18/3\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n3x + 2 \u003d 20", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n6x + 4 - 4 \u003d -32 - 4\n6x \u003d -36\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(6x)/6 \u003d -36/6\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n6x + 4 \u003d -32", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the addition property of equality to remove the constant.\n2x - 5 + 5 \u003d 7 + 5\n2x \u003d 12\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(2x)/2 \u003d 12/2\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n2x - 5 \u003d 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n-3x + 2 - 2 \u003d 5 - 2\n-3x \u003d 3\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(-3x)/-3 \u003d 3/-3\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n-3x + 2 \u003d 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n2x + 4 - 4 \u003d -2 - 4\n2x \u003d -6\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(2x)/2 \u003d -6/2\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n2x + 4 \u003d -2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-7", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\nx + 2 - 2 \u003d -5 - 2\nx \u003d -7\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\nx + 2 \u003d -5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n6x + 7 - 7 \u003d 43 - 7\n6x \u003d 36\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(6x)/6 \u003d 36/6\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n6x + 7 \u003d 43", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the addition property of equality to remove the constant.\n5x - 4 + 4 \u003d 16 + 4\n5x \u003d 20\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(5x)/5 \u003d 20/5\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n5x - 4 \u003d 16", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n-6x + 1 - 1 \u003d -11 - 1\n-6x \u003d -12\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(-6x)/-6 \u003d -12/-6\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n-6x + 1 \u003d -11", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n7x + 1 - 1 \u003d 43 - 1\n7x \u003d 42\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(7x)/7 \u003d 42/7\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n7x + 1 \u003d 43", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the addition property of equality to remove the constant.\n-5x - 4 + 4 \u003d -39 + 4\n-5x \u003d -35\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(-5x)/-5 \u003d -35/-5\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n-5x - 4 \u003d -39", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-7", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the addition property of equality to remove the constant.\n-7x - 5 + 5 \u003d 44 + 5\n-7x \u003d 49\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(-7x)/-7 \u003d 49/-7\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n-7x - 5 \u003d 44", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n4x + 1 - 1 \u003d -23 - 1\n4x \u003d -24\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(4x)/4 \u003d -24/4\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n4x + 1 \u003d -23", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the addition property of equality to remove the constant.\n4x - 5 + 5 \u003d -13 + 5\n4x \u003d -8\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(4x)/4 \u003d -8/4\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n4x - 5 \u003d -13", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the addition property of equality to remove the constant.\n2x - 1 + 1 \u003d -9 + 1\n2x \u003d -8\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(2x)/2 \u003d -8/2\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n2x - 1 \u003d -9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the addition property of equality to remove the constant.\n5x - 6 + 6 \u003d 29 + 6\n5x \u003d 35\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(5x)/5 \u003d 35/5\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n5x - 6 \u003d 29", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n7x + 1 - 1 \u003d -41 - 1\n7x \u003d -42\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(7x)/7 \u003d -42/7\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n7x + 1 \u003d -41", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n3x + 3 - 3 \u003d 9 - 3\n3x \u003d 6\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(3x)/3 \u003d 6/3\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n3x + 3 \u003d 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n4x + 7 - 7 \u003d 15 - 7\n4x \u003d 8\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(4x)/4 \u003d 8/4\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n4x + 7 \u003d 15", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\nx + 5 - 5 \u003d 9 - 5\nx \u003d 4\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\nx + 5 \u003d 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n-x + 5 - 5 \u003d 2 - 5\n-x \u003d -3\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(-x)/-1 \u003d -3/-1\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n-x + 5 \u003d 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n7x + 5 - 5 \u003d -23 - 5\n7x \u003d -28\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(7x)/7 \u003d -28/7\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n7x + 5 \u003d -23", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the addition property of equality to remove the constant.\n5x - 5 + 5 \u003d -25 + 5\n5x \u003d -20\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(5x)/5 \u003d -20/5\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n5x - 5 \u003d -25", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n-5x + 1 - 1 \u003d 6 - 1\n-5x \u003d 5\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(-5x)/-5 \u003d 5/-5\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n-5x + 1 \u003d 6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n6x + 2 - 2 \u003d -34 - 2\n6x \u003d -36\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(6x)/6 \u003d -36/6\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n6x + 2 \u003d -34", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n-x + 3 - 3 \u003d 9 - 3\n-x \u003d 6\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(-x)/-1 \u003d 6/-1\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n-x + 3 \u003d 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n6x + 6 - 6 \u003d -30 - 6\n6x \u003d -36\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(6x)/6 \u003d -36/6\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n6x + 6 \u003d -30", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n5x + 2 - 2 \u003d -3 - 2\n5x \u003d -5\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(5x)/5 \u003d -5/5\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n5x + 2 \u003d -3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\nx + 6 - 6 \u003d 0 - 6\nx \u003d -6\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\nx + 6 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the addition property of equality to remove the constant.\n3x - 5 + 5 \u003d -14 + 5\n3x \u003d -9\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(3x)/3 \u003d -9/3\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n3x - 5 \u003d -14", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the addition property of equality to remove the constant.\n6x - 4 + 4 \u003d 32 + 4\n6x \u003d 36\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(6x)/6 \u003d 36/6\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n6x - 4 \u003d 32", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n-x + 4 - 4 \u003d 2 - 4\n-x \u003d -2\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(-x)/-1 \u003d -2/-1\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n-x + 4 \u003d 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n5x + 3 - 3 \u003d -7 - 3\n5x \u003d -10\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(5x)/5 \u003d -10/5\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n5x + 3 \u003d -7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\nx + 3 - 3 \u003d 7 - 3\nx \u003d 4\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\nx + 3 \u003d 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n-2x + 3 - 3 \u003d 15 - 3\n-2x \u003d 12\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(-2x)/-2 \u003d 12/-2\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n-2x + 3 \u003d 15", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-5", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the addition property of equality to remove the constant.\n-5x - 5 + 5 \u003d 20 + 5\n-5x \u003d 25\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(-5x)/-5 \u003d 25/-5\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n-5x - 5 \u003d 20", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n2x + 2 - 2 \u003d -6 - 2\n2x \u003d -8\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(2x)/2 \u003d -8/2\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n2x + 2 \u003d -6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the addition property of equality to remove the constant.\n4x - 3 + 3 \u003d -27 + 3\n4x \u003d -24\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(4x)/4 \u003d -24/4\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n4x - 3 \u003d -27", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n5x + 3 - 3 \u003d 18 - 3\n5x \u003d 15\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(5x)/5 \u003d 15/5\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n5x + 3 \u003d 18", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-7", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\nx + 7 - 7 \u003d 0 - 7\nx \u003d -7\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\nx + 7 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the addition property of equality to remove the constant.\n3x - 4 + 4 \u003d 5 + 4\n3x \u003d 9\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(3x)/3 \u003d 9/3\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n3x - 4 \u003d 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n4x + 5 - 5 \u003d 29 - 5\n4x \u003d 24\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(4x)/4 \u003d 24/4\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n4x + 5 \u003d 29", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the addition property of equality to remove the constant.\n4x - 7 + 7 \u003d 13 + 7\n4x \u003d 20\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(4x)/4 \u003d 20/4\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n4x - 7 \u003d 13", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n4x + 5 - 5 \u003d 33 - 5\n4x \u003d 28\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(4x)/4 \u003d 28/4\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n4x + 5 \u003d 33", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n5x + 3 - 3 \u003d -17 - 3\n5x \u003d -20\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(5x)/5 \u003d -20/5\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n5x + 3 \u003d -17", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\nx + 7 - 7 \u003d 14 - 7\nx \u003d 7\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\nx + 7 \u003d 14", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n5x + 3 - 3 \u003d 13 - 3\n5x \u003d 10\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(5x)/5 \u003d 10/5\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n5x + 3 \u003d 13", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n3x + 2 - 2 \u003d 8 - 2\n3x \u003d 6\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(3x)/3 \u003d 6/3\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n3x + 2 \u003d 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n-6x + 4 - 4 \u003d -8 - 4\n-6x \u003d -12\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(-6x)/-6 \u003d -12/-6\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n-6x + 4 \u003d -8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n7x + 3 - 3 \u003d 52 - 3\n7x \u003d 49\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(7x)/7 \u003d 49/7\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n7x + 3 \u003d 52", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n-x + 3 - 3 \u003d 6 - 3\n-x \u003d 3\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(-x)/-1 \u003d 3/-1\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n-x + 3 \u003d 6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the addition property of equality to remove the constant.\n3x - 5 + 5 \u003d -2 + 5\n3x \u003d 3\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(3x)/3 \u003d 3/3\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n3x - 5 \u003d -2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the addition property of equality to remove the constant.\n-5x - 1 + 1 \u003d -31 + 1\n-5x \u003d -30\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(-5x)/-5 \u003d -30/-5\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n-5x - 1 \u003d -31", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n-4x + 7 - 7 \u003d 11 - 7\n-4x \u003d 4\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(-4x)/-4 \u003d 4/-4\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n-4x + 7 \u003d 11", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n7x + 2 - 2 \u003d 30 - 2\n7x \u003d 28\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(7x)/7 \u003d 28/7\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n7x + 2 \u003d 30", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-7", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n-5x + 5 - 5 \u003d 40 - 5\n-5x \u003d 35\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(-5x)/-5 \u003d 35/-5\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n-5x + 5 \u003d 40", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the addition property of equality to remove the constant.\n2x - 2 + 2 \u003d 2 + 2\n2x \u003d 4\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(2x)/2 \u003d 4/2\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n2x - 2 \u003d 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n4x + 5 - 5 \u003d -19 - 5\n4x \u003d -24\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(4x)/4 \u003d -24/4\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n4x + 5 \u003d -19", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n4x + 6 - 6 \u003d 22 - 6\n4x \u003d 16\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(4x)/4 \u003d 16/4\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n4x + 6 \u003d 22", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\nx + 6 - 6 \u003d 2 - 6\nx \u003d -4\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\nx + 6 \u003d 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n2x + 2 - 2 \u003d 10 - 2\n2x \u003d 8\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(2x)/2 \u003d 8/2\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n2x + 2 \u003d 10", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n-7x + 6 - 6 \u003d -29 - 6\n-7x \u003d -35\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(-7x)/-7 \u003d -35/-7\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n-7x + 6 \u003d -29", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n7x + 3 - 3 \u003d 52 - 3\n7x \u003d 49\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(7x)/7 \u003d 49/7\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n7x + 3 \u003d 52", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n-2x + 3 - 3 \u003d 11 - 3\n-2x \u003d 8\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(-2x)/-2 \u003d 8/-2\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n-2x + 3 \u003d 11", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n5x + 2 - 2 \u003d 17 - 2\n5x \u003d 15\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(5x)/5 \u003d 15/5\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n5x + 2 \u003d 17", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the addition property of equality to remove the constant.\n6x - 7 + 7 \u003d 29 + 7\n6x \u003d 36\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(6x)/6 \u003d 36/6\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n6x - 7 \u003d 29", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the addition property of equality to remove the constant.\nx - 7 + 7 \u003d -11 + 7\nx \u003d -4\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\nx - 7 \u003d -11", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the addition property of equality to remove the constant.\n-5x - 4 + 4 \u003d 1 + 4\n-5x \u003d 5\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(-5x)/-5 \u003d 5/-5\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n-5x - 4 \u003d 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the addition property of equality to remove the constant.\n4x - 6 + 6 \u003d -30 + 6\n4x \u003d -24\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(4x)/4 \u003d -24/4\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n4x - 6 \u003d -30", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n5x + 4 - 4 \u003d -16 - 4\n5x \u003d -20\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(5x)/5 \u003d -20/5\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n5x + 4 \u003d -16", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n-7x + 1 - 1 \u003d 15 - 1\n-7x \u003d 14\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(-7x)/-7 \u003d 14/-7\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n-7x + 1 \u003d 15", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6", "explanation": "We need to get x by itself on one side of the equation.\nUse the subtraction property of equality to remove the constant.\n-x + 1 - 1 \u003d 7 - 1\n-x \u003d 6\nNext, use the division property of equality to remove the coefficient\n(-x)/-1 \u003d 6/-1\n", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve the equation for x:\n-x + 1 \u003d 7", "type": "text"}
]}